norsecorp.com 2017-05-28

# Privacy Policy • Norse

Norse Corporation, (“Norse”) operates several websites including norse-corp.com and ipviking.com. It is Norse’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### WEBSITE VISITORS

Like most website operators, Norse collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Norse’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Norse’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Norse may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Norse also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. Norse only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### GATHERING OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

Certain visitors to Norse’s websites choose to interact with Norse in ways that require Norse to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Norse gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an evaluation account to provide their name, company, phone number, a username and email address. In each case, Norse collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Norse. Norse does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### AGGREGATED STATISTICS

Norse may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Norse checks and logs the risk score of each incoming IP address to its sites. Norse may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Norse does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

Norse discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Norse’s behalf or to provide services available at Norse’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Norse’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Norse will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Norse discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Norse believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Norse, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Norse website and have supplied your email address, Norse may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Norse and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Norse takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Norse uses cookies to help Norse identify and track visitors, their usage of Norse website, and their website access preferences. Norse visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Norse’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Norse’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### BUSINESS TRANSFERS

If Norse, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Norse goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Norse may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### ADS

Norse does not currently serve ads on our sites, however we reserve the right to introduce ads at any time. Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Norse and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Norse may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Norse’s sole discretion. Norse encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have an account on any of our sites, you should also check your account management page for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
